N E T F L I X  出 品
今天我很榮幸為大家介紹  已退役的威廉米勒上尉
I have the honor today to introduce you to Retired Captain William Miller.
他去過世界上所有你們想去的地方
He's been everywhere in the world you all wanna go...
外加你們不想去的地方
and a bunch of places you don't.
我今天請他來  是讓他在你們
I've asked him to come and talk to you all today
職業生涯很重要的時期  和你們談一談
at this important crossroad in your careers.
我現在就出去  這樣你們可以  坦誠和中肯地對話
I'm gonna step out so this conversation can be frank and to the point.
大概五年前  我當時在休假
About five years ago, when I was on leave...
我站在超市的麥片區
...I found myself standing in the middle of the cereal aisle at the Publix...
我的胳膊
with my arm
勒著一個人的脖子
around some guy's throat.
我勒得非常用力  他尿了褲子
I was squeezing so hard he pissed himself.
我當時的未婚妻不得不爬到我背上
My fiancee at the time had to climb on my back
拚命阻止我  我才沒殺了他
just so I didn't actually kill the guy.
你們知道我為什麼會這樣做嗎
Do you know why I was doing this
因為我讓他移開他的購物車  他沒動
Because he hadn't moved his cart when I asked.
我是精英中的精英
I was the best of the best,
我能封閉  控制  操縱
able to shut down, control, manipulate...
所有基本人類本能  只為了一個目標…
all basic human instincts towards one goal:
完成我的任務
the completion of my mission.
但是對其他人類使用極端暴力
But the effects of committing extreme violence on other human beings
會有生物效應
are biological
也有生理效應
and physiological.
這就是成為一名勇士的代價
That's the price of being a warrior.
山谷裡可以行動了嗎
Is everything clear in the valley
是的
Affirmative!
收到
Copy that.
行動
Enter, enter, enter!
走吧
Let's go!
* Make his fight on the hill In the early day
警察
* Constant chill deep inside
* Shouting gun, on they run Through the endless grey
* On the fight, for they are right Yes, by who's to say?
* For a hill, men would kill, why? They do not know
* Stiffened wounds test their pride
* Men of five, still alive
* Through the raging glow
* Gone insane from the pain That they surely know
* For whom the bell tolls
* Time marches on
* For whom the bell tolls...
進入
Enter, enter, enter.
我告訴你們
Let me inform you
你們已經被包圍了
that we have you surrounded.
所以  放下武器
So, put down your weapons,
走出來
come out of the building
手抱著頭
with your hands behind your head.
你說裡面有多少人
How many did you say were in there
不超過十個
No more than ten.
別  別出去
No, no, no!
你們守在這裡
You guys hold this position.
我們去找一個別的掩體
We're going to find other cover.
守在這裡
But hold here.
好的
Good.
羅德裡格斯
Rodriguez!
羅德裡格斯  你能不能守住
Rodriguez, can you hold your position
羅德裡格斯
Rodriguez!
媽的  不行啊
Fuck no!
我們需要後撤
We need to get back.
我再說一遍  守住位置
I said, maintain your positions.
堅持住
Hold on!
拉走他
Move him!Move him!
羅德裡格斯
Rodriguez
Rodriguez!
迭戈
Diego!
堅持住
Hold on!
前進
Advance.
打得好
Nice shot.
抓了你們  然後又看到你們
I'm so tired of arresting all of you
我已經受夠了
only to simply find you all here again.
啊  我的顧問來了
Oh, my adviser is here.
你準備好了嗎  兄弟
Ready, brother
美國在聽著呢
America is listening.
兄弟  拿走錢吧
Take the money, brother.
那可是40萬美元
It's $400,000.
你什麼都不會損失
You lose nothing.
錢已經在我手上了
I already have the money.
那洛雷亞呢
And... and Lorea
你剛才說什麼
What was it that you said
你想出賣你的老大
Now you're turning on your own boss
我知道他在哪裡
I know where he is.
操你媽的敢告密
Fucking snitch. Shh!
在哪裡
Where's that
墨西哥  迪士尼樂園
In Mexico Disneyland
哪裡
Where
不  不是
No, no.
兄弟  他躲在叢林裡
He's hiding in the jungle, my brother.
他不相信銀行或這類的東西  所以跑進了叢林
He went there because he doesn't trust banks or any of those things anymore.
先生
Sir
你可以找到他
You could find him.
混蛋  你是自尋死路
You just got yourself killed, fucker.
閉嘴
Silence!
抬頭  抬起你的小臉
Lift up, lift up your little face.
這個人是在說實話嗎
Is this guy telling me the truth
這裡還有人想攻擊警察嗎
Does anyone else out here want to try to assault a police officer
或者編個有關洛雷亞的假話
Or tell fairy tales about Mr. Lorea
把他們帶到卡車上
Take them to the trucks.
我去追她
I'll go after her.
快騎摩托車上去  快
Get up there with the bikes, now!
讓開
Move! Move!
桑提亞哥
Santiago Santiago
桑提亞哥  你在哪裡
Santiago, where are you
我在  迭戈
Yes, Diego
我也不知道我在哪裡
I don't know where I am.
但是她跑掉了  我跟丟了
But she escaped. I lost her.
出租車  去復活城
Taxi to the Resurrection City
你在那裡幹什麼
What were you doing there
警告我弟弟
Warning my brother.
老天爺
Jesus.
你說十二點  才他媽的十點半
You said it was going down at noon and it's ten fucking thirty.
是  但是我又不是總指揮  從來都不是
It wasn't my bust. It was never my bust.
他改了
He changed it.
-他們把他抓了   -我不知道
- They took him - I don't know.
他們把他抓了  你要把他弄出來
They took my brother, and you have to get him out.
-弄出來   -嗯
- Get him out - Yes.
他還活著就很幸運了
You're lucky he's still alive.
但是他不會活很久的
But he won't be alive for very long.
你根本就不應該讓你的愚蠢弟弟  攪進去這事
You never should've let your idiot brother get involved with this shit.
如果我告訴你我知道呢
What if I told you I know
我知道洛雷亞在哪裡
I know where Lorea is.
我知道錢在哪裡
I know where the money is.
你知道多久了
How long have you known
三個月
Three months.
那你為什麼沒告訴我
And why wouldn't you tell me that
因為我只是你的線人  對嗎
Because I'm just your informant, right
僅此而已
That's all I am
如果你有什麼想說的  現在就說出來
If you've got something to tell me, right now is the time to do it.
我…
I...
被提拔了
was given a promotion.
我負責運送滿車廂的錢
I deliver vans full of money...
去洛雷亞在叢林裡面的房子
to Lorea's house in the jungle.
他把錢都放在那裡
That's where he keeps the money.
他的房子就是保險箱
His house is a safe.
順便告你一件事
And just so you know,
迭戈和所有僱傭你的人  都被洛雷亞收買了
Lorea pays Diego and all of those men that hired you way too much money.
他們一直看著你瞎忙活
They've just been watching you chase your tail.
但是也許現在你可以真正做點事情
But now, maybe, you can actually do something.
你們的政府投入了很多時間
Your government has put a lot of time,
還有資金  來訓練你們
money, and training into all of you,
它絕不想浪費這個投資
and it does not want to lose that investment.
接下來幾個星期
Over the next few weeks,
會有大把的私人公司找你們
you will be bombarded with offers to take your skill set and use them
希望利用你的技能
in the private sector.
我也被他們騙過做這種事
I was suckered into the same thing.
但是我想和你們說的是
That's what I'm here to say,
我感到最純粹  最自豪的時刻
that I have never had a feeling as pure or proud
是肩上扛著國旗完成任務的時候
as completing a mission with our flag on my shoulder.
留在屬於你的地方
Stay where you belong.
謝謝
Thank you.
祝你們好運
Good luck.
這個演講你講過多少次了
How many times have you given that speech
這是第173次
It'll be 173.
還在計算生活裡的每件事嗎
Still keeping count of everything in your life
當然
Of course.
-嗯  很不錯的演講   -謝謝
- It's still a good speech. - Thank you.
你怎麼樣
How you been
我還行  你呢
I'm okay. You
你收到我的短信了
Did you get my text
嗯
Yeah.
所以  你怎麼看
So What's your take
你還找了誰
Who else do you have
你是第一個
I came to you first.
如果你能找來紅蒼蠅
If you can get Redfly,
我就干
I'll do it.
真的
Really
嗯
Yeah.
你覺得他會願意嗎
Do you think he's up for it
我只是覺得我們還欠他的
I just feel like we owe him.
另外…
Besides...
事情總是比想像的要難一點  對嗎
it's always a little harder than you think it's gonna be, right
把隊長找來  我就干
Get the captain, I'm in.
這棟房子有三個臥室
So... this is three bedroom
和一個半浴室
and one and a half baths.
後邊窗外的景色挺不錯
Nice view out the back window here.
光線還不錯
Gets good light.
廚房在這邊
Kitchen's right this way.
他們要12萬美元
They're asking $120,000.
-應該還會有點議價的空間   -嗯
- I think there's some flexibility there. - Yeah.
我覺得這個不適合我們  但還是謝謝你
I don't think this is the one for us. Thank you, though.
好吧  謝啦
All right, thank you.
嗨  我想買個公寓
Hey, I'm lookin' for a condo.
我聽說買公寓可以找你
I hear you're the guy to talk to.
-不好意思跑到這裡來找你   -嗨  哥們
- Sorry to track you down like this. - Hey, man.
我打給了你的辦公室
I called your office.
-看到你我很高興   -嗯  我也是
- It's good to see you. - Good to see you.
-你看上去不錯   -可不是麼
- You look great. - Ah, yeah, right.
-真的   -有一陣子沒聯繫了吧
- No, you do. - It's been a while, huh
我們有兩年沒有你的消息
Well, we didn't hear from you for a couple of years.
還以為你跑去叢林裡面做土著人去了
We thought you might have gone full native in the jungle.
嗯  我知道
Yeah, I know.
對不起
Sorry.
所以你怎麼樣
So, how are you
我還行吧
Uh... I'm okay.
-嗯  我聽說你和茉莉的事了   -嗯
- Yeah, I heard about you and Molly. - Yeah.
人之常情
It happens.
所以  我有個工作給你
So, I got a job for you.
做一周顧問  保證1.7萬的收入
Guaranteed 17 grand for a week of consulting.
只是偵查  不需要戰鬥  除非你想要
No action unless you want it. It's just a recce.
我退役了
I'm retired.
我知道
I know.
什麼工作
What is it
我們想拿下加布裡馬丁洛雷亞
We're gonna get Gabriel Martin Lorea.
你們不是找他很多年了嗎
Haven't you been trying to do that for years
是的
Yes.
我一直沒能找到他  現在終於找到了
I could never find him, and I finally did.
哥們  我沒法接
I can't do it, man.
現在我這裡忙的不可開交
There's more of this shit around now than ever.
那天安東尼還來找我  想讓我去非洲一個月
Anthony was down heretrying to get me to go to Africa for a month,
但是我…  我沒法去
- but I... I can't... I can't do it.
我需要你
I need you on this one.
不到一周的工作
- It's less than a week of work.
我非常想  我絕對需要錢
I would love to, God knows I could use the money,
我在養兩個家庭
but I'm supporting two households right now.
這個工作潛在的利潤豐厚
There's potential for significant upside on this.
哪怕你就看看我的準備工作
Will you just take a look at my work on it
-你去看班尼的拳賽嗎   -去
- Are you going to Benny's fight - Yeah.
我要去接泰絲  我已經晚了  茉莉會殺了我
I gotta pick up Tess. I'm late. Molly's gonna kill me.
-坐我車吧   -行
- Just ride with me, okay - All right.
所以分開了  茉莉還允許你來這裡
Molly's still letting you over here, even after the split
只能進車庫而已
Only in the garage.
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
泰絲
Tess!
-還喝酒嗎   -當然
- Still drink - Oh, yeah.
啤酒
Want a beer
湯姆  請支付
媽的
Ah, shit.
你和那女人有一腿嗎
You sleeping with this woman
會計  記賬的那個  給你信息的那個
The accountant, the bean counter who gave you all the information.
我猜她應該挺火辣
I'm guessing she's hot.
什麼意思
What's that supposed to mean
我就是注意到這些年來  你的線人
Oh, well, I just noticed, over the years,
通常都是非常有吸引力的女性
your informants tend to be very attractive women.
沒有
No, I'm not.
為什麼沒有
Why not
情況已經夠複雜了
It's a fucked-up enough situation as it is.
嗨  寶貝
Hey, babe.
嗨  泰絲
Hey, Tess!
桑提亞哥
Santiago.
喔  都長這麼大了
Wow, so grown up, man.
我可不覺得
Oh, I don't know about that.
我服役第一年才掙1.7萬
I made 17 grand my first year in the service, man.
如果那時候你告訴我  我會拒絕一周掙1.7萬的工作…
If you told me then I'd be passing that up for a week's work...
不用擔心  她十五歲  我們說的話  她一個字都聽不進去
Don't worry about her, she's 15. She's not listening to a word we say.
1.7萬隻是偵查的費用
Seventeen grand is just for the recce.
如果我們決定進一步行動  很可能會掙得更多
But if we decide to move forward, this could be a whole lot more than that.
我和那邊的代理談好了
I've cut a deal with the agency down there.
我們查獲的所有財物  可留下四分之一
We keep 25% of anything we seize.
我估計  他有超過7500萬美元的現金
I've got estimateshe's got over $75 million in cash with him.
-我操   -沒錯
- Holy shit. - Yeah.
假設這筆錢真的在那裡
Let's say the money is there.
我們怎麼把錢拿回來
How do we get paid
這活兒很大  需要真正的計劃
'Cause this shit is serious, and it takes real planning.
-你應該知道的   -我在聖約翰找了個律師
- And you know that. - I've got a lawyer in St. John's
他幫我設立了一個海外空殼保安公司
who set up an offshore shell security operation
可以給我們付一輩子的薪水獎金
that's ready to pay out a salary and bonuses for the rest of our lives.
就像其他人發工資一樣
It'll justcome in like any other paycheck.
你能不能看一下我的計劃
Will you take a look at my work on it
我不想看  因為看了我就會不停的想
No, I don't want to see that because then I can't unsee it.
整個行動是非法的  對吧
This operation is... illegal, right
這個不是非法的
This is not illegal.
我的公司和外國政府的代理簽了合約
My company's under contract to an agency of a foreign government.
再說就算是非法的  你過去的行動
And besides, even if it was illegal, most of the live fire you've done's been
從嚴格意義上講  都是違反日內瓦公約的
against the Geneva Convention, technically, so...
就這樣  你應該有更好的說詞  這完全是兩碼事
Come on, you're a better salesman than that. This is a very different thing.
我馬上回來
I'll be right back.
所以你想讓他回去工作
So you're trying to get him to go back to work
或許吧
Maybe.
為什麼
Why
沒什麼
No reason.
你覺得你媽還會讓他去嗎
You think your mom would still let him go
我媽
My mom
當然啦
Of course.
她沒問題
She's not the problem.
在他們強迫他退役後  他就沒工作過
He hasn't worked since they forced him to retire.
你父親是個好人
Your dad's a good man.
你不應該這樣說他
You shouldn't be too hard on him.
* Listen to the wind blow Watch the sun rise...
所以你繼續賣公寓  我繼續干我的
So, I guess you'll just keep selling condos,
直到有一天我的膝蓋跑不動了
and I'll run and gun until my knees finally blow out.
或者你可以幹一票  不需要我
Or you could do this without me.
我可以
I could.
但是我不想要
But I don't wanna,
因為我覺得我們應該過更好的生活
'cause I say we deserve better, man.
多少次我們帶著2000萬的現金到處飛
How many times did we fly around with 20 million bucks at our feet
錢就在腳下  然後都給了一些人渣  我們一分都沒拿
to pay off some cockroach somewhere, and we never took a dime
-操  你還被打過四槍   -五槍
- Hell, you've been shot four times. - Five.
你為了你的國家被打過五槍
You've been shot five times for your country,
現在你連一輛新卡車都買不起
and you can't even afford a new truck.
這才是真的犯罪
That's the real crime.
-多保重  泰絲   -再見
- Good to see you, Tess. - Good to see you.
你還會來嗎
You coming back
嗯  給我二十分鐘  我先把她放下
Yeah, I'll be back in 20, I gotta drop her off.
鐵頭去嗎
Is Ironhead in
只要你去
Only if you are.
-就看一看   -好吧
- Just take a look. - Fine.
我看一看吧  別再提我的卡車
I'll take a look. Leave my truck outta this.
這和我的卡車無關
This isn't about my truck.
有關係  完全和你的卡車有關係
Yes, it is. That's exactly what this is about!
* Running in the shadows
* Damn your love, damn your lies
-你媽會來接你  聽到嗎   -好
- Your mom will pick you up, okay - Yep.
* Break the silence
嗨
Hey!
我愛你
I love you.
我想你
I miss you.
* And if you don't love me now
* You will never love me again
* I can still hear you saying
- You would never break the chain - Never break the chain
他怎麼說
What'd he say
他說他看一看
He's taking a look at it.
他不一定會同意
He may not be up for this.
你也知道這麼複雜的情況  他是最厲害的
You know he's the best with something this complex.
而且他現在正需要錢
And he needs this right now.
好吧
All right.
這個媽的太鬱悶了
This shit is fuckin' depressing.
別這樣
C'mon.
讓你弟弟玩玩  支持他一下
Let your brother have some fun. Support him.
從他出生那天起  我就一直在支持他
I've been supporting him since the day he was born.
這孩子是萬里挑一的天才
That kid's a one-in-a-million talent,
結果在這裡給一幫鄉巴佬當小丑
going out there, playing the fucking clown to a bunch of hillbillies.
喂  我的後援在哪兒呢
Ah, yeah, where are my corner men
我的天  看看誰來了
Holy shit, look who it is!
班尼  你怎麼樣  天吶
What's up, Benny Oh, holy shit!
我的天吶
Oh, God!
今晚來得挺是時候
Hell of a night for you to show.
-很高興又見面了   -是啊
- It's great to see you, man. - You as well.
你怎麼越來越醜了
Hey! Every day you're uglier.
啊  你個混蛋
Ah, you little shithead.
見到你真好
Good to see you.
你們收到我的短信了
Did you boys get my text
嗯
Yeah
鯰魚
Fish
我需要個飛行員  沒你我幹不了
I need a pilot. I can't do this thing without you.
哥們  我說不好
I don't know, man.
我剛剛有個寶寶
I got the new baby now,
我家那位不支持我再幹那種活了
and my lady isn't into me doing this kinda shit anymore.
什麼意思
What... What does that mean
你看短信了嗎  這可能會永遠改變你和寶寶的生活
Did you read the text This can change you and that baby's life forever.
之前不是說什麼回到祖國
What happened to that bullshit about going back to your mother's homeland
幫助那裡的人管理自己的屁話  現在怎麼了
and empowering the people to police themselves
再說  我丟了執照  現在也飛不了了
Anyway, I lost my license. I can't even fly right now.
我不需要一個有執照的飛行員
Well, I don't need a pilot with a license.
我和那裡的軍隊合作  我只需要一個  能信任的飛行員
I'm in with the army down there. I just need a pilot I can trust.
嗯  我覺得不行
Yeah, I don't think so.
好吧
Okay.
洛雷亞在毀滅他們的國家
Lorea is destroying that country.
我們要做的只是幹掉一個很壞的壞蛋
So we get to take out a very bad man, and, oh, by the way,
而且最後還能像買彩票中個大獎一樣
there's a winning lottery ticket stuck to the bottom of your cowboy boot.
這是每個人都求之不得的機會
Every guy in that gym would jump at this.
專心點  大家  今晚是比賽夜
Come on, focus, guys! It's fight night.
嗯  你別管這些狗屁
Yeah, don't worry about that bullshit.
對不起  班尼
Sorry, Benny.
你準備好了嗎
You ready for this
當然啦
Hell yeah.
走吧
Let's go.
我不是想說你說的是狗屁
I didn't mean to call your shit bullshit.
沒事的
It's all right.
我被抓到了
I got busted.
不是什麼大事
It's not a big deal.
其實也算是大事了
Actually, it's a big deal.
可卡因
Coke
天吶  弗蘭基
Jesus, Frankie.
嚴格來講  是暫扣  還在審查中
Technically, it's a suspension. I'm still under review.
你呢  你怎麼想
Well, what about you What are you gonna do
我說過如果紅蒼蠅去的話  我也去
I said if Redfly's in, I'm in.
喂  大家專注點
Come on, stick with me here, guys.
班尼  我支持你
Oh, I'm with you, Benny.
但是你支持我嗎
But are you with me
你去嗎
Are you in
你知道我會去的
You know I am.
你去哪我去哪
I go where you go.
我想也是  班尼就是個勇士
That's what I thought. Benny stands tall.
來自科羅拉多的紅羽重量
From Red Feather Lakes, Colorado,
88公斤  一米九的個子
standing six foot three, weighing in at 195 pounds,
現在歡迎班米勒
I bring you... Ben Miller!
去吧  班尼
Go, Ben!
加油
Come on!
上吧  班尼
Let's go, Benny!
兄弟們  乾杯
Cheers, man.
班尼  小心  穩住
Benny, take it easy! Nice and slow!
我看了看你的計劃  弄得不錯
I took a look at your folder. It's good work.
謝謝
Thank you.
你需要五個人和一個飛行員
You need five guys and a pilot.
歡迎班尼
Yeah, Benny!
幹掉他  班尼
Go! Get him, Benny!
哥們  你好啊
What's up, brother
你還差一個入境計劃
The only thing missing is your entry plan.
我給我們每人弄了一整套假護照
I have a full set of bullshit passports waiting for us.
我們作為電力顧問過海關
We go through immigration as power line consultants.
一旦入境
Once we're in-country,
他們沒有面部識別攝像頭
they don't have any facial recognition cameras yet, so...
我們就可以消失了
we're ghosts.
所以結論是
So what's the verdict
如果你們都去的話  我也去偵查
I'm in for the recce if you guys are.
確定
- You sure - Yeah, just the recce though.
嗯  但只做偵查  不開火
No live fire.
-可以   -嗯
- That's all right. - Okay.
鯰魚
Fish
什麼時候
When is it
我們週四出發
We leave Thursday.
好
Okay.
現在開始
And here we go!
加油  班尼  上吧
Come on, Benny! Let's go!
好樣的  班尼
All right, Benny!
該開工了
it's time to work.
* Whoa, thought it was a nightmare
* Lord, it was so true
* They told me don't go walking slow
* The devil's on the loose
* Better run through the jungle
* Whoa, don't look back to see
歡迎來到巴西
通訊器
Comms.
分一下
Pass those out.
我們現在在洛雷亞的後院
We're in Lorea's backyard.
所以這傢伙為什麼不用袋子  最起碼用個保險箱
So what's this guy got against banks At least a safe.
這個房子就是保險箱
The house is the safe.
我到大門了
I'm at the gate.
看上去所有的東西都只弄對了82%
This looks like everything was done about 82% right.
東西都齊了  但是這些攝像頭
They got all the toys out here, but these cameras aren't even aimed
都沒對準最薄弱的攻擊點
at the weakest breach point.
你女朋友會像平常那樣來送錢
Your girlfriend's making her normal money drop
嗯
Yeah.
她會錄下來房子裡面的情況
She's prepared to record the inside of the house.
教皇…
Pope...
教皇  我看到小孩了  他和孩子們一起住
Pope, I have kids over here. Does he have kids living in here with him
這下情況會變得格外複雜
'Cause that's gonna make things a whole lot more complicated
我可不是來幹這個的
and is not what I signed up for.
家人不是問題
The family's not the problem.
他們是答案
They're the answer.
為什麼
Why
教堂
Church.
洛雷亞非常虔誠
Lorea's very devout.
每個週日早上  他會
Every Sunday morning,
派三個衛兵去六點的主日崇拜
he sends three guards to the 6:00 a.m. service.
等他們回來  他再派剩下的人
When they get back, he sends the rest of the team,
還有他的家人進去城裡參加彌撒
along with his family, into town to mass.
這時候房子裡
That leaves him
就剩他一個人和三個衛兵  這就是我們的機會
and three guards in that house, and that's our window.
他為什麼那樣做
Why would he do that
他擔心有人會綁架他的孩子
Worried about someone taking his kids.
他從來不離開他的錢
And he never leaves his money.
另外  我想他不相信會有人有膽量
Also, I don't think he believes anyone actually has the balls
敢來這裡搶他
to come out here and rob him.
也許是因為這本身就是個很蠢的想法
It's probably 'cause it's a stupid idea.
教皇  我看見你女朋友來了
Pope, I got your girlfriend coming up right now.
我靠
Holy shit.
她很漂亮哦
She is beautiful, man.
我就知道
I fucking knew it.
滾蛋
Fuck off.
我操
God damn.
這邊即將開始行刑
I got an execution about to go down over here.
你在網球場
Are you at the tennis courts
嗯
Yeah.
嗯  那就是他常用的地方
Yeah, that's his spot.
原諒我  神父
Perdoname, padre.
她為什麼要幹這個
Why is she doing this
她希望我能把她弟弟弄出監獄
She hopes I can get her little brother out of jail.
是你把他抓進監獄的
Did you put him in jail
不是
Not really
你好
Buenas
我猜這給她帶來了風險
I'm guessing that's putting her at some risk.
我差點忘了我之前為什麼退役的
Man, I almost forgot why I got out of this business.
總是看到黑暗面
Shit gets so dark so quick.
該死  這裡有地面感應器
Oh, shit, we got ground sensors here, boys.
你觸發了嗎
Did you hit one
不知道  不確定
I don't know, I'm not sure.
班尼  兩個騎摩托車的人  朝你那邊開去了
Benny, I got two guys on motorbikes coming your way.
班尼  耐心等待  我這就過去掩護你
Hold tight, Benny. I'm trying to get out there to cover you.
洛雷亞先生  下午好
Good afternoon, Mr. Lorea.
突然覺得
A stock boy job at
在沃爾瑪管理貨品的工作也不錯
Walmart's starting to look pretty good right now, boys.
看上去是對的
It looks good to me.
很好
Good.
好了
Okay.
先生  謝謝
Thank you, sir.
我安全了  他們朝你開回去了
I'm clear. They're coming back to you.
我們他媽的撤吧
Let's get the fuck outta here.
…你會尿褲子的
You were gonna piss yourself.
我正準備說似曾相識的部分
I was getting onto the deja vu part, man.
所以計劃是什麼
So what's the plan
他們準備好跨境行動了嗎
Are their guys prepared to operate across the border
這個行動範圍多大
What's the scope of this thing
最好的辦法就是週日突襲
Sunday soft hit is the way to do it.
不然你帶一隻軍隊進去  挑起的是一場戰爭
Otherwise, you bring in an army, you'd start a fucking war up there.
所以你什麼時候  要給這裡的代理演示計劃
Mm-hmm. So, when do you need to present to the agency down here
我不確定我要告訴他們
I'm not sure I wanna tell them.
為什麼
Why
我們都偵察過那裡了
We saw the place.
漏洞百出
It's full of holes.
所以也許我們不需要告訴他們
So maybe we don't tell them...
我們自己干
...and we do this thing ourselves.
什麼
What
我們每個人拿了1.7萬
Now, we each took 17 grand...
來幫助稽毒部隊畫地圖
to help the narcotics unit map out
計劃這個行動
and plan this fuckin' thing.
我告訴過你我原本就不太想幫這幫人
I told you I wasn't even comfortable helping them do it.
現在你想我們自己干
Now you want us to do it by ourselves
幹掉一幫他媽的毒販
Kill a bunch of fuckin' narcos
如果我們像你說的  抓住週日的機會  大部分人在教堂
If we hit that window, like you said, when they're at church,
我們只需要幹掉洛雷亞
nobody but Lorea gets killed.
這個我可以接受
And I'm okay with that.
這邊的代理知道這件事嗎
Does the agency down here even know about this
什麼意思
What do you mean
哥們  說吧  別他媽的吞吞吐吐的
Come on, man! Don't fuck around.
誰給我們付的錢
Who paid our fees
有點複雜  嚴格來講…
It's complicated,technically...
你們是通過一個有限責任公司付的
you guys were paid through an LLC.
別  沒那麼複雜
Mm, no, not that complicated.
就是10萬塊  錢他媽的從哪裡來的
It's $100,000. Where the fuck did it come from
我買單
I'll get the bill.
謝啦
Thanks.
這次行動真不錯
Great trip, boys.
完全變成一次胡闖亂搞了
It's turning out to be some full-on cowboy shit.
錢是誰的
Whose money is it, huh
是我自己的
- It was my money. - Jeez.
你在想什麼
What were you thinking
這有改變什麼嗎
What Does that change anything
有
Yeah, man.
你他媽的騙了我們
You fucking lied to us.
不  我沒有
No, I didn't lie to you.
我問你們來這裡
I asked you guys to come down here,
偵查和制定一個計劃
do reconnaissance, and make a plan.
現在我們可以按計劃自己行動
Now, we can execute that plan alone
拿走所有的錢
and take all of the money,
或者你們可以滾蛋  我再找一個這裡的團隊行動
or you guys can fuck off, and I'll bring the team from down here in.
但我確定  如果我那樣做的話  這個混蛋一定會得到風聲
But I assure you, if I do that, this fucker will find out about it,
他一定跑路  我需要抓到他
and he'll be gone, and I need this guy.
你知道這個世界上有多少壞蛋嗎
You know how many fucking bad men are out there all over the world
嗯  這是我最後一個
Yeah, well, this is my last one.
也許你不相信
And you may not believe it,
但過去三年裡  我一直在這裡
but I have been here for the last three years of my life,
想給這裡做點改變  但這裡還是一塌糊塗
trying to make a difference, but it's a fucking mess.
全是因為洛雷亞
And it's all because of Lorea.
一想到我們過去十七年裡所做的一切
The thought of leaving everything we've done behind for the last 17 years,
卻最終兩手空空…
with nothing to show for it...
去你媽的兩手空空
Fuck you, nothing to show for it.
聽我說
Look, if...
如果我們能在任何其它職業  幹出一半我們的成績
If we had accomplished half the things that we've accomplished
我們會一輩子衣食無憂
in any other profession, we'd be set for life.
喂  兄弟
Hey, man,
那是我們要做的犧牲
that's the deal we cut.
-這個犧牲不怎麼樣   -是啊…
- Well, it's a shitty deal. - Yeah, well...
因為這傢伙是個他媽的英雄
Because this man's a goddamn hero,
然而他都沒法把孩子送去上大學
and he can't even send his kids to college.
鯰魚是我認識的最厲害的飛行員  卻因為狗屁可卡因被調銷執照
And Fish's the most talented pilot I know, and he's grounded on a bullshit coke rap.
你弟弟要被暴打多少次  就為了幾百…
And how many times can your brother get the shit knocked out of him for...
我沒有被暴打  那場我贏了
I didn't get the shit beat out of me. I won that fight.
對不起  班尼
Sorry, Benny.
你還要做多少次演講
And how many more pep talks can you possibly give
我受夠了
I'm done, man.
兩個膝蓋都不行了
Both knees are shot.
去年的脖子手術之後  身體更不好了
That neck operation I got last year made the whole thing worse.
所以  關鍵是
So, the question is,
我們是否最終利用我們的技能  為自己謀點利
do we finally get to use our skills for our own benefit
來真正改變我們的生活
and actually change something
所以我們要不要行動
So, are we doing this
我他媽的怎麼知道
How the fuck am I supposed to know
這小子還沒有拿到最重要的情報
This guy doesn't come through with the onekey piece of intel
我們沒法做決定
we needto make this decision.
也許她在給我們設個圈套
For all we know, she could be setting us up
只為了救她弟弟而已
to get her brother back.
明天就知道了
We'll know tomorrow.
她今天應該都錄下來了
She should have been recording that whole thing today.
好吧  如果結果沒問題的話
All right, if it does come back clean,
你準備怎麼開展週日行動
how would you do the Sunday morning version
我還沒想好
I haven't thought about it.
狗屁  你肯定早就想好了
Bullshit, you can't help yourself.
好吧
All right.
這次迅速行動  我們有四十分鐘時間進去完成任務
In the first pop, you'd have 40 minutes to get in, get the job done,
在家人從教堂回來之前出來
and get out before the family comes home from church.
必須按時出來
That's a hard out.
我們需要攻破圍欄
We need to breach the fence,
搜索區域  找到並制服衛兵
sweep the premises, find and subdue the guards,
在監控室裡清空硬盤
scrub the hard drives in the security room,
解決掉洛雷亞  找到錢  把錢放進816公斤的袋子裡
get rid of Lorea, find the money, pack the money into 18 hundred-pound bags,
然後拖八百米到最近的車
and then hoof it half a mile to the nearest vehicle.
只有兩個方法出去
There's only two ways out:
從前面的柵欄  翻下我們走過的山
the fence in the front, or over the mountain we came down,
我太老了  幹不了這個
and I'm too old for that.
我們需要用一輛他們的麵包車
We need to use one of their vans.
院子裡有兩輛
There were two vans in the courtyard.
但是如果他家人開它們去教堂  那我們就沒戲了
But if the family uses those vans to go to church, then we got nothing.
所以我們還需要一輛麵包車
So we need another van.
你的女友能解決這件事嗎
Can your girl work that out
我問問她
I can ask her.
你的航空導遊還能聯繫上嗎
Still got your aviation guy down here
因為我們需要一個能負重的直升機
'Cause we would need a heavy-lift helicopter in 32 hours
32小時內帶我們越過安第斯山  飛到海邊
to get us over the Andes and to the ocean.
不知道  我給他打個電話看看
I don't know, but I'll give him a call.
太棒了  老大重出江湖了
Oh, yeah! Big dog is back!
紅蒼蠅要發財了  兄弟們
Redfly's gonna be rich, boys!
這才像回事兒
Now we're talkin'.
嗨
Hello.
Hola.
謝謝  再見
Thank you. Have a good day.
謝謝
Thank you.
就這樣
That's it
我不知道
I don't know.
兩杯咖啡  謝謝
Miss, two coffees, please.
-我弟弟呢   -嗯
- My brother. - Yeah.
我可能還需要你再做一件事情
I might need you to do one more thing for me.
你能弄一輛麵包車
Can you get an extra van...
進去那裡嗎  週日上午
into the compound, Sunday morning
如果這樣的話  他們會知道是我
If I did that, they're going to know it's me.
而且他下面的人遲早都是死路一條
And everyone who works for him ends up dead, sooner or later.
如果你能在週日上午  給我弄一輛麵包車
If you can get me an extra van in there Sunday morning...
我會給你和你弟弟弄到新護照和錢
I will get you and your brother out of the country
把你們弄出國
with new papers and money.
多少錢
How much
200萬
Two million.
Two million
嗯
Yes.
你只有幾個小時救我弟弟
And you'll only have a couple hours to get my brother
我會有辦法
I'll find a way.
但是我需要你把車弄進大門裡
But I need that van inside those gates.
好的
Okay.
-可以   -嗯
- Yeah - Yes.
我去弄車
I'll get the van.
但如果我們不能永遠消失  你一旦行動  我們就死定了
But if we're not gone forever after you make your move, we are dead.
你會消失的
You'll be gone.
好
Yeah.
謝謝
Thank you.
嗨  大家
Hey, fellas.
看看這個
Take a look at this.
天啊  教皇
Jesus, Pope!
你在這裡計劃些什麼
What the hell were you planning here
就是這個
Exactly this.
每一隻槍  子彈
Every single gun,bullet,
甚至他媽的牙籤  都是在這個國家弄來的
and fucking toothpick here's been sourced in-country.
目的是把這次行動  嫁禍到當地的敵對幫派
The idea is to pin this on a local rival gang.
是誰不相信這位女士的
Now, who was it that didn't trust this lady
因為她不僅僅會給我們弄到車  還給我們弄來了這個
'Cause not only is she going to get us that extra van, but she got us this.
這就是我們的目標  洛雷亞
There's our man, Lorea.
還有
And, oh!
看到他後面是什麼了嗎
Look at what's there behind him.
看起來像是錢
Looks like money to me.
那起碼是3500萬
- There's gotta be about 35 million there.
這可說不好
We don't know that.
不管多少  那是一大筆錢
Whatever it is, it's a lot.
你的錢準備怎麼花
What are you gonna do with your share, huh
班傑明  錢還沒到手呢  先別想那麼多
Never spend your money until it's in your pocket, Benjamin.
我就是想說  我準備弄台法拉利
Well, I'm just sayin', I'm gonna get that Ferrari, man.
真是不俗
How original.
那直升機呢
What about the bird
他說如果我們帶300萬去  直升機就會在
Well, he said if we're there with three million bucks, he'll be there.
我們有直升機
So we got a bird,
我們有麵包車
we got a van,
我們確定了洛雷亞和錢都在房子裡
we got Lorea confirmed in the house with the money.
好吧  給我一分鐘
All right, give me... give me a minute.
你知道嗎  如果我們還在服役的話  衝你這個點子
Uh, you know, if you had pulled this shit when we were active duty,
我會送你上軍事法庭
I would have court-martialed your ass.
這樣吧  我們晚上吃個飯
Look, why don't we all just have a dinner tonight,
好好喝一頓  我請客  然後你們早上可以回家
get drunk, on me, and you all can go home in the morning
去他媽的
Nah, fuck that.
我不能回去
I can't.
只是我…
Somehow, I just...
在這裡改變了想法了  你知道嗎
...ended up against it here. You know
我的退休金快沒了
I'm burning through my pension.
茉莉的工資也不夠
Molly's job doesn't cut it.
我賣不出去公寓  來拯救我該死的生活
I can't sell condos to save my fucking life.
我唯一能做的就是照顧好女兒
The only thing I have is taking care of these girls.
嗯
Yeah.
嗯  我明白
Yeah, I understand that.
媽的  我一直懷念這種生活
Fuck, I missed this.
就好像他們奪走了你最好的二十年  然後把你趕出來
It's like they take your best 20 years, and then spit you out.
沒錯
Yeah.
但我總是會去想犯過的錯誤
I just can't stop thinking about the mistakes.
什麼錯誤
What mistakes
媽的  哥們
Fuck, man.
所有的錯誤
All of 'em.
你退役後  沒感覺好一些
- Didn't get better when you got out
沒有
No.
唯一讓我感覺好點的  就是你把槍放在我手裡時
Only thing that made it feel better is when you put a gun in my hand.
所以  我想就這麼辦
So, I guess that's what we'll do.
好的  首先最重要的是
All right, first things first:
安全
safety.
沒有醫療救援  沒有地面支援
There is nomedevac. There is no ground support.
如果受傷  我們就要帶著傷走出去
Any injuries we sustain, we're walking out with.
記住  你們每個人都有一個醫療包
Be mindful, each of you has a medical kit in your bag.
第二點
Number two:
從今晚之後  你不能再回到之前的普通生活
you cannot go back to your normal life after tonight.
你們不要有誤解
Make no mistake about it.
我們要做的事是犯罪
What we are about to do is criminal.
我們肩上沒有國旗
We do not have the flag on our shoulders, and no amount of bullshit
不管我們給自己怎麼解釋  都不會改變這個事實
that we tell ourselves is gonna change that.
如果我們幹的好
If we do our job right,
我們將會犯下一項謀殺罪  和一項持械搶劫罪
we will be committing one murder and one armed robbery.
你們需要接受這個事實
You guys need to own the fact that you are desecrating
就是你們在褻瀆所發過的誓
most of the oaths you ever took.
第三
Third:
家人
family.
如果他們沒去教堂  或者提前回來了  那麼行動取消  完全停止
If they don't go to church, or if they come home early,
他們不是我們的目標
it's an abort. Full stop. They are not who we came for.
最後
And lastly,
現在依然可以選擇回家
it's not too late to go home.
我們和教皇有個協議
We had an agreement with Pope,
我們已經完成了
and we fulfilled that.
任何人想離開都可以立刻離開  我們不會看扁他
Any man here who wants to walk away now can do so knowing they're the best of us.
但一定要現在就走
But it's gotta be now.
我就是要確認我們離開房子前
I wanna make sure we're not leaving that house
要解決掉洛雷亞
without taking care of Lorea.
如果他在他應該在的地方  我們就會拿下他
If he's there like he's supposed to be, we'll get him.
凌晨三點出發
We leave at 0300.
還好這些人這麼虔誠
It's a good thing these guys are so devout.
我們爸曾經說過
Our dad used to say,
如果下雨就代表  上帝今天不需要我們去教堂
"When it's raining, it means God didn't need us in church today."
他還說去天堂是為了宜人氣候
He also said you go to heaven
下地獄是為了有人作陪
for the climate and hell for the company.
實際上是馬克吐溫說的
Actually, I think Mark Twain said that.
好了  無線電靜默  警惕點
All right, keep the radio clear, let's stay awake here.
有多少人上車了  數一數
How many is that getting in Count it.
麵包車裡進去七個
Seven getting in the van.
有人看到洛雷亞嗎
Anybody see Lorea
沒有  我們沒看到他出來
Negative. We never saw him come out.
他老婆和兩個小孩和一個司機同車
The wife and two kids are in with a single driver.
一家人離開了
The family's left the building.
重複一遍  一家人離開了
Repeat, family are all clear.
好的  我們準備好
All right, let's get ready here.
操  教皇  這個女生值得留下來
Damn, Pope, this lady is a keeper.
準時  聰明  還很勇敢
Punctual, smart, and brave as shit.
-你好   -什麼事
- Good day. - What's this
我來送這個麵包車
I'm here to drop off this van,
然後我哥哥帶我回家
and then my brother is taking me home.
那個白癡沒和我說
That idiot didn't tell me.
她進去了
She's in.She's in.
好了
Here we go.
班  你第一個  安全了呼叫
Ben, you're first hit. Call when it's secure.
這麼大的雨  衛兵都會在裡面
With this rain, the guards are gonna be inside.
收到
Roger.
可以了  她走了
All clear, she's gone.
收到
Copy.
好  我們進去
All right, we're going in.
前面安全
Front gate secure.
廚房一個衛兵拿下
One guard secured in the kitchen.
班尼  來房子裡
Ben, come to the house.
收到
Roger.
我在前門這裡
I'm at the front door.
等等  班尼  等等
Hold, Benny. Hold.
電視房間有威脅
Threat in the TV room.
我從側面過去
We're gonna go around the side.
那邊怎麼了
What's going on in there
沒事  班尼  注意觀察洛雷亞
All clear, Benny. Eyes out for Lorea.
他肯定聽到我們了
He sure as fuck heard us now.
我進來了
I'm coming in.
監控室設置炸藥
Setting charges to the security room.
剛才怎麼回事
What was that
我不得不打了第二個衛兵的腿  他們帶他去廚房
We had to shoot the second guard in the leg.
下來了
- They're taking him to the kitchen. - Coming down.
快點
Come on.
保險線在燃燒
Fuse is burning.
看到他了嗎
Any trace of him
她說他從來不會離開
She said he never leaves.
沒人
We got nothing.
這傢伙是個幽靈
This guy's a ghost.
所有人都來辦公室  立刻
Everyone to the office, right now.
這他媽的怎麼回事
What the fuck
洛雷亞呢
And Lorea
沒有  只有幾個袋子
Nothing. A couple of bags.
他跑了
He's gone.
帶著錢
With the money.
你的女朋友把我們出賣了  教皇
Your girl gave us up, Pope.
我們媽的趕緊走吧
We gotta get the fuck outta here.
不…
No, no, no, no, no, no.
你們聞到什麼了嗎
What's that smell like to you
聞起來像是搞砸了
Like a serious fuck-up.
不是…
No.
油漆
Paint.
這個房子是保險櫃
The house is the safe.
這個房子是媽的保險櫃
The house is the fucking safe.
班尼  過來幫我  快點
Benny, help me move this. Come on.
-我抓邊上   -放這邊
- I'll take the edge. - Over there.
快點  兄弟  快
Go, come on. Come on, man. Come on!
我操
- Holy shit! - Come on.
快
Go. Move, move.
-天啊   -鯰魚  該我了
- Oh, my God! - Fish, I'm up.
快點
Come on, guys!
天啊
Holy shit!
我說什麼來著
What'd I tell you, boys
老天爺
Jesus Christ!
他媽的  看啊
Fucking God! Look at it!
一直到上面
It goes all the way up!
快干
Let's go!
我們需要袋子
We're gonna need some bags.
我再拿個袋子
I'll get another bag!
繼續
Keep it coming.
怎麼了
What's wrong
如果錢還在這裡  意味著他還在這裡
If the money's still here, it means he's still here.
哥們  他已經跑了
He's gone, man.
這裡還有
We got more!
後牆也有
Back wall, too.
專注點
Just concentrate.
哦  我們發了
Oh, we're just gettin' rich!
還有多少時間
How much time we got
八分鐘
Eight minutes.
米勒  那邊行了
Millers, enough of that over there.
我們要開始把它們拿上車
We gotta start getting this shit to the van.
好  交給我們
Yeah, we got this.
-哥們  快點   -保持警惕
- Come on, bro. - Keep your eyes open.
耶  婊子們
Yeah, bitches!
這個  拿上這個  我去開車
Here, take these. I'm gonna go get the van.
-下面見   -好的
- Meet me there. - Yes, sir.
小心
Careful.
經典
Classic.
天啊
Jesus Christ.
-快幫忙   -快點
- Help us, man! - Come on!Come on!
來吧  這邊
Come on. Over there.
天啊
Holy shit!
我們還需要袋子  看看還能不能找到
We're gonna need more bags. See if you can find something.
收到
On it.
我和你說
I tell you one thing, man,
你可以告訴你女兒們不用學習了
you can tell your girls they can stop studying
因為老爸能花錢送她們進哈佛了
'cause Daddy's just gonna buy their way into Harvard!
天啊  這他媽的太多錢了
Holy shit, this is a fuckload of money!
快拿走
Grab some of those and go.
時間還剩多久
How are we on time
我們還有時間再搬兩趟
We got time for a couple more loads.
-確定   -拿上這幾個下去
- You sure - Grab those and bring 'em down.
大家
Guys!
我又找到一堵牆
I got another wall over here!
-天啊   -操
- Holy shit! - Shit!
到處都是
It's everywhere.
操他媽的
Well, fuck me!
整個房子都是
It's the whole fucking house.
怎麼了
What's up
車滿了
The van's full, man!
行了  我們走吧
It's all good. We gotta go.
你他媽的在幹什麼
What the hell are you doing
別挖了  這裡還有這麼多要運
Stop digging more out. We got all this to deal with.
再來幾包
A couple more loads.
你知道嗎  湯姆  和你干了十年
You know, in the ten years I've been working with you, Tom,
你從來沒有錯過一個撤離時間
you have never missed a hard out!
我給我們留了十五分鐘的空餘
I gave us a 15-minute cushion.
十二分鐘去教堂  四十分鐘禮拜  十二分鐘回來
It's 12 minutes to the church, a 40-minute service, 12 minutes back.
五分鐘裝車
Add 5 minutes to load in and out of the van,
我們還有七分鐘比他們先出去  我們沒問題的
and we can subtract 7 to beat them to the exit route.
明白
We will be fine!
看看這些錢
All right God damn it, look at all this money!
再來幾趟
Just a couple more loads!
不幹了
Fuck this!
時間到了  我們要走了
Time's up. We gotta go.
我想再搜查一次洛雷亞
I want one more sweep for Lorea.
明白
All right
然後全部燒掉
And then we burn it all down.
好
Okay,
我把最後一袋裝車
I'll get these last one loaded down there,
你準備好點火喊一聲
and you call out when you're ready to light it up.
行動
Move.
Move!
快點  我們要走了
Come on, we gotta go!
點火吧
Lighting it up.
我們在打什麼
What are we shooting at in here
是洛雷亞嗎
Is that Lorea
他死了
He's dead.
很好
Good.
我被打中了
I'm hit.
操
Shit!
-小心   -哪裡
- Take it easy. - Where
左邊
Left side.
穿過去了嗎
Did it go through
嗯  穿過去了
Yeah, it went through.
我沒事  沒事的
- I'll be fine. - It'll be okay.
-去拿止血的東西   -直接穿過去了  沒事的
- Get the clot kit. - Straight through.
你沒事的
You'll be okay.
很快就好了
You'll be all right.
繼續呼吸
Just breathe.
我還好
I'm okay.
走吧
All right. Let go.
-我說過這是一個很蠢的想法   -是的  你說過
- Told you this was a stupid idea. - Yeah, you sure did.
主日崇拜結束了
Sunday school's over, boys.
他們回來了
They're back.
該死
Oh, shit!
-那一家人   -不是  第一批衛兵
- The family - No, the first shift of guards.
-你還行   -我沒事
- You okay - I'm all right.
你能走嗎
You gonna be able to move
-我們沒有擔架   -嗯
- We don't got a stretcher. - Yeah.
幫我把止血的敷上
Just help me get my kit back on.
我們每個人背一包錢
All right, we can each take a backpack of cash,
我們從後面穿過叢林  然後消失
we go out through the back into the jungle, and we're gone.
-我來負責行動的損失   -去他的吧
- I'll cover the cost of the operation. - Fuck that.
不
No.
我們要帶鐵頭安全回家
We are bringing Ironhead home safe.
而不是拖他過叢林
Not dragging him through the jungle.
而且我們不能把這媽的錢留給他們
And we're not leaving them any of this fucking money.
好  所以我們把錢全燒了  然後走
Right, so we burn it all down and go.
那個麵包車裡大概有1個億
There's about $100 million for them waiting in the van out there.
我們需要迅速把他們找到幹掉
We need to hunt and shoot quickly.
幹掉喊出來  我不想要任何驚喜
Call out your kills. I don't want any fuckin' surprises.
明白
Got it
好的
All right.
我們上吧
Let's do this.
你們兩個那邊  我們從前面下去
You two go that way, we'll come down the front.
我沒事的
I'm all right.
我們行動吧
Let's just do it.
好嗎
All right.
好
走吧
Let's go.
大傢伙們  開始吧
Here we go, fellas.
前廳已擊斃兩個
That's two down in the front hall.
第三個
That's three.
第四個
That's four.
回到大門
Get back to the gate.
我肯定他們在那裡放了人
I'm sure they dropped a few guys out there.
這就去
On the way.
有人看到衛兵進來坐的車嗎
Anybody got eyes on that SUV the guards came in
因為我們需要那輛車
Because we're gonna need it.
我已經在裝車了
I'm already loading it up.
大家都出去了嗎
Is everybody out of there
教皇安全
Coast's clear.
全部安全
All clear.
另一個麵包車剛剛經過  開進行車道
Another van of guys just passed me in the driveway.
鯰魚開車過來
Catfish is coming around with the van.
你在幹什麼  快走
What are you doing Come on! Let's go!
班尼
Benny!
嗨
Hey!
快走
Let's go, man! Hustle!
操
Fuck!
媽的
怎麼了
What
什麼怎麼了
What do you mean, what
剛才幹的太爛了  我們從來沒有  留下這麼個爛攤子
That was a shit job back there, man. We don't leave messes like that!
我們這裡怎麼辦  一家人在等著進入
What do we do up here I've got the family waiting to go in.
慢點
Take it slow.
你女朋友在這裡
Your girlfriend's here.
-你安全出來了吧   -嗯
- Did you get out okay - Yes.
我們快了
We're almost there. Help me.
幫幫我
Vamos.
都堆在這裡  我來過稱
Just load 'em up, and I'll weigh 'em.
你的人呢
Where's your guy
他會來的
He'll be here.
就這個飛機讓我們他媽的怎麼弄
What the fuck we gonna do with that thing
威廉
William.
哈比比
- Habibi.
-你來了   -你知道我靠譜
- You made it. - Count on me.
被蚊子咬了
Mosquito bite
嗯  小意思
Yeah, a little one.
感覺比看上去更糟糕
Feels worse than it looks.
這個小飛機  我們怎麼裝進去
Now how the hell are we all gonna fit in that
你準備好  就過來吧
- Come when you're ready. - Copy.
可以點一下數
Feel free to count it.
我知道去哪裡找你
I know where to find you.
瞧
Voila!
網裝不下全部的
It won't all fit in the net!
剩下的放裡面
We gotta get the rest on it inside!
我不知道那個稱是不是壞了
I don't know if that scale's fucked up,
但是他說我們這裡有2720公斤
but he's telling me we got 6,000 pounds here.
那可是2億5000萬美元
That's $250 million.
我們偷了2億5000萬
We stole 250 million
我一定要買輛法拉利
I'm definitely getting that Ferrari!
-你確定   -走吧
- Are you sure - Let's go!
如果稱夠準的話
If that scale is even close to being right,
我們有負重問題
we're gonna have a weight issue.
什麼問題  這個直升機可以載四千公斤
What's the issue This helo can carry 9,000 pounds.
飛六百米高  可以載四千公斤
That's 9,000 at 2,000 feet.
如果我們想去海邊  就要飛過安第斯山脈
If we want to get to the ocean, we gotta fly over the fucking Andes, man.
我們真的留2億美元在跑道上
Are we really leaving $200 million on the fucking runway
好吧  應該可以  走吧
Okay, she'll make it. Let's go!
她怎麼辦  我們已經超重了
What's your plan for her We're already overweight as it is.
我們承諾帶他們越境去秘魯
We promised them a ride over the border into Peru.
我們要兌現承諾
And we're gonna stand by that!
我們現在讓你們走
Okay, we're gonna let you go now.
謝謝
Thank you.
但是我需要知道一件事
I just need to know something.
我叫什麼
What's my name
我不知道
I... I don't know.
你的那個朋友呢  他叫什麼
What about your buddy back there What's his name
我不知道
I don't know.
他說他沒法告訴我
He said he couldn't tell me.
接下來你要說的話
Okay, I want you to be real careful...
要深思熟慮再開口
about what you're about to say
因為唯一能  把我們和他們聯繫在一起的人是你
because the only thing that ties us to them is you.
當你們終於上床時
Now, when you finally had sex,
你翻過身來看著他的眼睛  然後問
and you rolled over and looked him in the eye and said,
"你叫什麼名字"  他是怎麼說的
"What's your real name" What did he say
從沒發生過這種事
That never happened.
我可以現在去問他
I can just go ask him.
他從沒說過他哪裡來的
He never told me where he was from.
他說你們一起當過兵
He said that you served together...
還有你很誠實
and that you were honest.
他為什麼說這個
Why'd he say that
因為我問他
Because I asked him if...
會不會害怕你背叛他
if he wasn't afraid of you cheating him.
那就是為什麼
That's why.
一切都還好吧
Everything all right
不
No!
這裡是300萬美元
Here's three million dollars.
兩張票和簽證去澳大利亞悉尼
And two tickets with visas to Sydney, Australia.
去機場路上  在這個貨運公司停一下
On the way to the airport, stop at this shipping company.
把這些盒子寄到悉尼的這個酒店
Make sure to send the boxes to this hotel in Sydney.
你知道那裡遠遠超過7500萬
You know that's a lot more than 75 million dollars in there.
什麼意思
What does that mean
那裡不只是洛雷亞的錢
It's not just Lorea's money in there.
會有很多人來找你們
A lot more people are gonna come looking after you.
我能對付  你們不能待在南美洲
I can deal with that. But do not stay in South America
因為他們會找到你  他們會殺了你
because they will find you and they will kill you.
答應我你不會留在這裡
Promise me that you won't stay here.
-好的   -答應我
- Yes! - Promise me!
我答應
I promise you.
我怎麼…  怎麼聯繫你
How... How do I contact you
你不能
You can't.
你每件事都做得很好
You did everything right.
這是你應得的
You deserve this.
好好照顧自己
Take care of yourselves.
謝謝
Thank you.
去吧
Go!
她在撒謊
She's lying.
她沒有
No, she's not.
這樣做會有後果的
There are consequences to this shit.
你知道我們本該怎麼做嗎
You know what we should have done
那樣做  你永遠也無法抹去
That's one you wouldn't come back from.
再高一點  重量會拖住飛機
The weight drags at higher altitudes.
我想在飛到安第斯前保持1500米以下
I'd like to stay under 5,000 feet till we hit the Andes.
四小時到海邊
Ocean in four hours.
明白  幹得好
Roger that. Nice work.
我會試著從兩個山峰中穿過
I'm gonna try between these two bigger peaks.
找到這個我在地圖上看到的山谷
Find this valley I saw on the map.
收到
Roger.
還差一程就到安第斯了
Just one last push through the Andes.
你覺得有多高
How high do you think that is
應該是3350米  沒法飛這麼高
It's gotta be 11,000. Can't fly that high.
應該不需要  沿著低谷飛
Shouldn't have to. Head for that lower ridge.
大家怎麼樣
How are we doing up here, boys
我們能過得去嗎
Can we make it over
我不知道
I don't know.
這裡是怎麼回事
What the fuck is going on up here
上吧
Go for it.
好的  寶貝
All right, baby.All right, baby.
加油
Come on, now.
好的  寶貝
All right, baby.
-我們到了臨界線了   -夠近了
- We're redlining, man. - It's close, though.
太多負重  負重太他媽多了
It's too much weight. It's too much fucking weight.
這樣我們過不去
We're never gonna make it.
-什麼意思   -意思是我們要丟掉一些錢
- What does that mean - It means we're losing fucking money.
你想把5000萬丟在原始森林
You wanna leave $50 million in the middle of the jungle
你還想到海邊嗎
Do you wanna get to the ocean
好吧  去幹吧
All right, go do it.
交給我
I got it!
好  我看看
All right, let me check.
飛機感覺怎麼樣
How's she feeling now
好多了
That's feeling better.
你可以的
Come on.Come on.
加油
Come on.
鯰魚  你他媽的在搞什麼
What the fuck are you doing, Catfish
其中一個齒輪箱爆了
One of the gearboxes is blown.
什麼
What
我不想打轉
I don't want to go into a spin.
我們可能有麻煩了
Okay, we might be in trouble here.
我在失去高度
I'm losing altitude.
我們得降落  現在得降落
Ah, we should land. We should land now.
在這裡迫降  我們都得死
Crash-land here, and we all die.
我在想辦法找個平地
I'm trying to get her back to flat.
收到  準備迫降
Roger. Prepare for a hard landing!
這個山脊另一邊應該有一個農場
There should be a farmer's field on the other side of that ridge.
-我們飛上來的時候有路過   -我記得
- We passed it on the way up. - I remember it.
下面拉個袋子  我們沒法降落
I can't land this with that bag under us.
我們需要把錢丟掉  也許這樣我們才不會都死掉
We should lose the money, maybe we don't die.
丟掉錢  不然我們都得死
Lose the money, or we're all gonna die!
試試外面的卸載裝置
Hit the external load release.
在牆上
It's on the wall!
班  快拉桿
Pull the lever, Ben!
拉桿不工作
It didn't work!
貨鉤上面應該還有一個
There should be a manual override
人工卸載桿
on the cargo hook.
讓我過去
Let me through!
班尼
Benny!
好吧  我會試試降落這邊
All right, I'm gonna try to land here.
我得跳下去了
I gotta jump!
班尼
Benny!
沒降落好
Bad landing.
鯰魚
Fish! Fish!
-你沒事吧   -是的  我還好
- You all right - Yeah, I think so.I think so.
班尼
Yo, Benny!
Benny!
我在這裡
I'm here!
過來  我們得走了
Come on, we gotta move.
快點
Come on!
我們快走吧
Let's get our shit outta here.
去上面
Try and get up to it.
-鯰魚   -該死
- Fish! - I need oxygen.
大家都沒事吧
Everybody okay
-是的   -嗯
Yeah.
他們在打開網
They'reinto the fucking net.
我們什麼計劃
What's the plan here
我們拿上錢  越過山  去海邊
We're gonna get that money over that mountain to the ocean.
班尼  去森林線那邊掩護我們
Benny, cover us from under that tree line there.
鯰魚  去上邊找個位置
Fish, you take position up there.
他們在種可卡因  所以他們
That's cocaine they're growing, so they may have weapons trained on us
可能有槍從那邊的房子對著我們
from those buildings right there.
無線電還工作嗎
We got working radios
-不行了  通信器壞了   -用手勢
- No, comms are dead. - Go with hand signals.
教皇和我過去  盡量平和點
Pope and I will get out there and look as peaceful as we can.
如果安全的話  我們會給一個手勢
We'll give you a hand signal when we think it's secure.
-上吧   -班尼
- Let's move. - Benny.
請後退
Please step back.
先生
Sirs!
後退  這不是你們的
Step back, please, that is not yours.
你們是誰
Who are you
你們哪個部門的
Who are you with
我們是陸軍
We're with the army.
我們是顧問
We are advisers.
你應該叫一個急救直升機
You should call a rescue helicopter.
-在路上   -嗯
- It's coming. - Yes.
所以這段時間
In the meantime,
就你們幾個  而且沒穿軍裝
you are aloneand don't have any uniforms.
這個可以解決
Okay, that can be resolved.
其它事故的乘客呢
But what about the other passengers from the accident
我們可以談談
We can talk about that.
但是告訴你的人停止偷我們的東西
But tell your people to stop stealing our property.
這裡是我們的土地
These are our lands.
緝毒局  搞砸了
You fucked up, DEA.
不是的  冷靜點
No, no, no. Calm down. Calm down.
先生  小心那個武器
Sir, careful with that weapon.
我們不是緝毒局的
- We're not DEA.We're not DEA.
喂  你們有後援  對吧
- Tell your guy to put his gun down.
-冷靜  住手   -我們很冷靜
- Stay calm. Stop.  - We are calm.
教皇  他在拿什麼  是武器嗎
Pope, what's he reaching for A weapon
教皇  你收到…
Pope, do you cop...
別動  不要再靠近
Stay right there. Don't get any closer.
媽的  怎麼搞的
Fuck! What the hell, man
不
No!
-兇手  混蛋   -離開那裡
- Assholes! Murderers! - Get out of there!
離錢遠點  離開那裡
Get away from the money! Get away from there!
-操   -不
- Fuck! - No!
拜託  我們只需要馬和騾子  然後我們就走
We need horses or mules, please, and then we will get out of here.
班尼  把這些人帶去村裡
Benny, get these people back up toward the village.
鯰魚  把錢放騾子上  我們他媽的趕快走
Fish, get this money on some mules. Let's get the fuck out of here.
退後
Get back!
起來
Get up!
女士  起來
Get up! Get up, lady!
送我去見上帝
Send me to God.
走  繼續走
Go! Keep going!
媽的
Fuck.
給這些驢裝上鞍子  袋子放上去
All right, let's get these donkeys saddled up, get the bags on 'em.
教皇呢
Where's Pope
他在那邊
He's up there.
這個是買騾子的
That is for the mules.
這個給那些家庭的
That is for the families.
這個給你的
That is for you.
我們達成共識了嗎
Are we in agreement
很好
Good.
我們很抱歉發生了這種事
We're very sorry for what happened.
我們非常感謝你的合作
And we very much appreciate your cooperation.
走吧
Come on.
抱歉  孩子
Sorry, kid.
那些人已經付了他們的債
Those men have paid their debt!
讓他們過去
Let them pass.
你給他們賠償損失了嗎
Did you pay for the damage
嗯
Yeah.
多少
How much
牲口200萬  每個家庭100萬
Two hundred for the animals. A million for the families.
你們誰先開槍的
Which one of you shot first
我不知道
I don't know.
我們需要注意點自己
We need to watch ourselves here.
嗯  是的
Yeah, we do.
他媽的什麼意思
What the hell does that mean
沒事
Nothin'.
意思就是我們需要注意點自己  就這樣
It just means we gotta watch ourselves, that's all.
明白
Roger that.
我們走了多遠
How far have we gone
大概走了十二公里了
We've gone about 12 clicks.
到達船那裡還需要一天半  也許兩天
To get to the boat, it's another day and a half, maybe two.
現在要是有點火就太好了
Well, a fire would be righteous.
洛雷亞的人在追蹤我們
Lorea's guys will be on our tail.
點火的煙會暴露我們  我們要不生火野營
Smoke from a fire will give us away. We cold camp.
我們現在是和惡魔共舞
Well, we're dancing with the devil now.
共舞
Dancing
我們上飛機就已經在共舞了
We were dancing when we got on the plane to come down here.
現在已經在滾床單了
I would call this full intercourse.
哥們  你怎麼樣了
How you doing, bud
棒極了
Golden.
給你
Here.
班尼  你是個好人
You're a good man, Benny.
我們這種人可不多了
We're a dyin' breed, boys.
我們可不是
No, we're not.
這個世界總是需要能一家一家  維持秩序的人
The world's always going to need somebody to go door-to-door to hold the line.
警察就是一家一家維持秩序的人
Cops go door-to-door and hold the line.
我們曾經是勇士
We were warriors.
有時候很難想起這一點
Well, it's hard to remember that sometimes.
嗯  是啊
Yeah, it is.
你想說什麼
What are you talking about
我太急於開槍了  你我都知道
I was too quick on the trigger. You know it, and I know it.
是我殺了這些人
I killed those people.
不  不只是你
No, you didn't.
我們都參與了
We all did.
* Come you masters of war
* You that build the big guns
* You that build the death planes
* You that build all the bombs
* You that hide behind walls
* You that hide behind desks
* I just want you to know I can see through your masks
* You that never done nothin'
* But build to destroy
* You play with my world
* Like it's your little toy
* You put a gun in my hand
* And you hide from my eyes
* And you turn and run farther When the fast bullets fly
這絕對是以前走私者走的山路
This is definitely the old smuggler's trail!
一直跟著走到上面
We should just keep following it all the way up.
小心
Come on.
別逼我這麼緊  這裡很陡峭的
Stop pushing on me, man. It's steep here.
可不是  我們在他媽的山的側面
Obviously, man, we're on the side of a fucking mountain!
閉嘴  別分心
Just shut up and concentrate!
老天爺
Jesus Christ!
-快點  繼續走   -操你媽的
- Come on, just go. - Fuck you.
你認真的
Oh, really
繼續走
Keep going!
-停   -哦  你要鬧脾氣
- Stop. - You wanna do this
操
Oh, fuck!
你他媽的在笑什麼
What the fuck are you laughing at
哥們  那可是個活生生的動物
That was a living animal, man.
本來可能是我們其中一個掉下去
It could have been any one of us.
你在擔心一個他媽的驢子
You're worried about the fucking donkey
哥們  你需要冷靜點
You need to get your shit straight here, man.
-什麼  我   -對  你
- What Me - Yeah, you.
-你在指責我嗎   -就是因為你
You're pointing fingers at me
-我們才在這個爛攤子裡   -你他媽的什麼意思
- You're the reason we're in this mess. - Oh, how the fuck is that
對  你每一塊錢都想帶走  是不是
Yeah, you had to grab every dollar you could get your hands on, didn't you
你兩個月前就可以幹掉洛雷亞  這樣我們不會來這裡了
You could have gotten Lorea two monthsago! We didn't need to be here.
好了
All right.
操他媽的
Fucking bullshit!
我們所有人都有責任  沒錯吧
We're all on the hook, are we not
操他媽的馬  夠了
God damn this fucking horse! Stop it!
-好了  沒事的   -放鬆
- Yes. It's fine. - Relax. Relax.
我們現在先不要在傷口撒鹽了  行吧
We're not picking at the fucking scab right now, okay
一步一步往前走
One foot in front of the other.
好吧  走吧
All right Come on.
我們走吧
Let's go. Jesus fucking Christ.
你確定要我趕走騾子
Are you sure you want me to get rid of the mules
這塊岩石有六米高
This rock side's 20-foot deep.
騾子沒法上來
We're not getting the mules through.
嗯  現在只能靠我們自己了
Yeah, it's on us now!
看這些騾子
Look at the mules.
嗯  如果我們能翻過這個
Well, if we can get over this,
應該都是下坡路一直到海邊了
it should be all downhill to the ocean from here.
拿到了
I got it.I got it.I got it.
好了  上來吧
All right, come on up!
-幹得好   -你也是
- Nice work. - You, too.
我剛才說了很多狗屁話
Look, I talked a lot of shit back there.
我不是那個意思
I didn't mean that.
-別再想了   -不  這…
- Don't worry about it. - No, no, it's...
這是我的錯
This is on me.
-都是我的錯   -不  哥們  這是…
- It's... all on me. - No, man, it's...
我也參與進來了
I'm on the hook for this.
事已至此了
You know It is what it is.
是啊  事已至此了
Yeah, it is what it is.
但我確實有點混蛋
I am a bit of a dick, though.
這裡可以冷的可以凍住一個  愛斯基摩人的屁眼了
You could freeze an Eskimo's asshole out here.
我要求點火
I demand a fire.
我們要不生火野營
We cold camp.
操你媽的
Fuck you.
這是我的操你媽錢
This is my "fuck you" money.
你他媽的在幹什麼
Dude, what the fuck are you doing
我們人手不夠運這些錢
We don't have enough men to carry this money,
那還不如用來取暖呢
so we might as well be warm.
天吶
Oh, Jesus.
老天啊
Jesus Christ.
-我才不在乎   -這個瘋子
- That's more like it. - Este loco...
哦  天吶
Oh! Oh, my God! Holy shit.
這才叫篝火
Now that's a fire!
-操   -該死的
- Oh, shit! Shit. - Ah, Fuck.
我被打中了
I'm hit!
班尼  你沒事吧
Benny, you all right
嗯  沒事  只是擦傷了肩膀
Yeah, I'm fine. Just grazed my shoulder.
槍手在山脊線上
Shooter's up on the ridge line.
他太喜歡我了  我就呆在這裡吸引火力
Oh, he likes me so much. I'll stay here, hold his fire.
你們從側面迂迴
You guys go around the side.
教皇  你可以出去嗎
Pope, can you step out
沿著小路上去
Work up the trailhead.
好
All right.
右邊迂迴  確認下面沒有人上來
Flank right, make sure no one else is coming up below.
我從後面掩護你
I'll cut up behind you.
班尼  你沒事吧
Benny, you all right
是的  我沒事  我們在這裡守著  等你到位
Yeah, I'm fine. We'll hold down here until you get into position.
我覺得教皇已經到位了
I think Pope's in position right now.
好的  行動
Yeah, let's move.
湯姆
Tom!
湯姆  起來…
Tom. Come on... Come on.
拜託  湯姆  拜託你
Come on, Tom. Come on, man.
拜託  老兄  拜託了
Come on, man. Come on...
我看看
Let me see.Let me see.
他媽的
Oh, my God!
我們把他捲起來
Let's get him wrapped up.
我們需要繼續上路
We need to keep moving.
你他媽的在說什麼
What the fuck are you talking about
你個沒心沒肺狗娘養的
You're a heartless son of a bitch!
就是你的那堆火把他害死的
It was your little fire that got him fucking killed!
夠了
Stop it.
都別打了
Stop this shit.Stop this shit.
都他媽的住手
Fucking stop this!
住手
Stop this shit! Stop it!
-住手   -操你媽的  班尼
- Stop this shit! - Fuck you, Benny! Fuck you!
不是火暴露的我們
It wasn't the fire that gave us away.
這個孩子是那個村裡的
That kid was from the village.
他已經跟蹤我們幾天了
He's been tracking us for days.
很明顯他就想一槍打死湯姆
He obviously wanted a clear shot at Tom.
他想要殺他報仇
He wanted him.
但我們必須繼續他媽的往前走
But we do have to get the fuck out of here,
而且我們要帶上所有的錢
and we are taking all of that money with us.
湯姆的家人應該得到這錢
Tom's family deserves it!
我們也是
And so do we.
好了  我們把他捲起來  帶下山
All right, let's wrap him up. We carry him down.
安息吧  兄弟
Rest in peace, brother.
安息
You rest in peace.
* 世間有位母親 *
*  Somewhere there's a mother *
* 在為她的孩子哭泣 *
*  Crying for her boy *
* 他是一名空中突擊隊員 *
*  He is an airborne ranger *
* 帶著命令去部署 *
*  With orders to deploy *
* 世間有位父親 *
*  Somewhere there's a father *
* 在為他的孩子哭泣 *
*  Crying for his son *
* 他的兒子是一名空中突擊隊員 *
*  His son was an airborne ranger *
* 要贏取一場戰者 *
*  With a war to be won *
* 世間有位女兒 *
*  Somewhere there's a daughter *
* 在為他的爸爸哭泣 *
*  Crying for her dad *
* 他是一名空中突擊隊員 *
*  He was an airborne ranger *
* 而他現在只包裹著一面旗幟 *
*  Now he's just a folded flag *
* 不要為他哭泣 *
*  Don't you cry for him *
* 他不需要你的憐惜 *
*  He don't need your sympathy *
* 他是一名空中突擊隊員 *
*  He is an airborne ranger *
* 這是他最好的結果 *
*  It's the best that he can be *
我們和有船的那個人晚了幾天碰面
How late are we to meet the guy with the boat
五天
Five days.
天吶
Jesus.
你覺得他還在嗎
You think he's still there
我什麼也看不見
I can't see shit.
我們需要派一個人先下去
We need to get one of us down there.
我們中間有人能過去再回來嗎
Think one of you can make it there and back
我去
I'll go.
班尼  你的西班牙語很爛
Your Spanish sucks, Benny.
我可以的
I got it.
你確定
You sure
三疊
Three
嗯
Yeah.
你找的人叫敗家子
You're looking for the Hijo Prodigo.
班尼  注意你身後
Benny, watch your six.
你們也是
You watch yours.
我想說幾句話  你們在聽嗎
I'm gonna say something. Are you listening
嗯
Yeah.
我們要振作起來
We gotta get back on our game.
不要再低迷  現在就要振作  明白嗎
Enough of this. It stops now. You understand
明白
Copy that.
好
Good.
你覺得你殺過多少人
How many people do you think you've killed
什麼
What
你有聽到
You heard me.
該殺多少殺多少
As many as I had to.
你為什麼會想知道這個
Why would you ever wanna know that
-四十三   -天吶
- Forty-three. - Jesus!
確認的
Confirmed.
你還在計算所有的東西
You keep count of everything, huh
嗯
Yep.
你睡眠怎麼樣
How's your sleep
比想像中的好
I guess better than it should be.
你還好吧
You all right
船還在
The boat's there.
我給了他一半錢
I gave him half the money.
希望他會等我們
I hope he waits.
我沒進城
I didn't go into town,
但是看起來  不管誰是首領
but it looks like whoever's in charge there...
他們組織了一個兒童軍隊在搜索我們
has a... kindergarten army that's looking for us.
多少人
How many of them
兩三個專業的
Two or three pros,
二十個重武裝的青少年
20 heavily-armed teenagers.
旁邊鎮子呢
What about the next town over
要再往南走160公里
It's over 100 miles to the south.
反正我估計他們每個鎮子都布好人了
I'm sure they've got every town covered anyway.
應該是洛雷亞剩下的人
Must be what's left of Lorea's guys.
所以我們闖過去
So we go through 'em.
闖過去
Through them
什麼意思  把他們全幹掉
What, do you mean we mow them all down
還有別的選擇嗎
What's the alternative here
我可沒準備好幹掉鎮裡
I'm not prepared to wipe out every teenager in that town
所有的青少年  僅僅為了這批貨
just to get through with this cargo.
這批貨
This cargo
那批貨呢
What about that cargo
你願意為他做嗎
Will you do it for him
湯姆為了這筆錢而死
Tom died for this money,
我們不帶著這筆錢就不能離開
and we're not leaving this country without it!
他不是為了這筆錢而死的  他是因為這筆錢而死的
He didn't die for that money, he died because of it!
哥們  他們還是孩子
They're just kids, man.
我們就不能帶上貨趁晚上溜過去嗎
Can't we carry itout through the dark
不可能  這裡有超過一百個袋子
It's over 100 bags. There's no way.
我和他談談
Let me talk to him.
哥們  班尼是說他們還是孩子
Look, Benny's telling us these are kids, man.
我不敢相信…  我不敢相信我會讓這種事發生
I can't believe... I can't believe I let this happen.
聽好了  我們都是自願來的
Look, we all came here of our own free will.
是  但是…
Yeah, but...
我以為我們可以…  我以為我們可以辦到
I thought we could... I thought we could do this.
是啊
Yeah.
我們自作自受
And we got what we deserved.
對不起
I'm sorry.
嗯  我也是
Yeah, me, too.
-但是我們不能這樣做   -我知道
- But we can't do this. - I know.
我知道
I know.
我們不能幹掉他們
We can't just... go through 'em.
我不知道我剛才在想什麼
I don't know what I was saying.
沒事了
It's all right.
我們只需要把湯姆帶回家
We've just gotta get Tom home.
這就是最重要的
That's all that matters.
我們要怎麼做到
How are we gonna do that
我們帶上這些繼續往下走
We keep carrying him down.
我們只帶上平時的裝備
We fill our days packs with whatever we can...
能帶多少帶多少
Whatever we can carry, and that's it.
那麼剩下的怎麼辦
What do we do with the rest of it
操
Fuck.
這他媽的
Fuck me.
這可行
That'll work.
很快就會下雪了
Snow will be coming in soon.
沒人會再看到
Nobody'll ever see it again.
好
Good.
來吧  我們繼續
All right, let's keep going.
把他放下一會兒
Let's put him down for a second.
我們晚了
We're running behind.
班尼  你去吧  太陽快出來了
Benny, you should go. The sun's coming up.
我們三十分鐘後在海灣見
We'll meet you down at the cove in 30.
-小心點   -嗯
- All right. Be careful. - Always.
謝謝你在等我們
Thank you for waiting.
船準備好了
The boat is ready.
別  等一下
No, wait. Whoa.
有人嗎
Is there anyone
看上去是廢棄的
It looks abandoned.
掩護我
Cover me.
站住  手舉起來
Stop! Hands up!
-手舉起來   -等等
- Put your hands up!  - Wait! Wait!
聽好
Listen!
小兄弟  小心那只槍  不要對著我
Little brother, be careful with that gun. Don't point it at me.
我講英語
I speak English!
袋子…  袋子裡是什麼
What's in the bag What is that
是我們的朋友
It's our friend.
他死了
He's dead.
-我打給老大   -別  千萬不要
- I call boss.  - No, don't do that.
停  別動
- Stop!
我們不想和你惹麻煩
We don't have any problem with you.
大家說是吧
Right, guys
-我們不想惹麻煩  對嗎   -不惹麻煩
- We don't have a problem with him. - No problem.
-我要開槍了   -別  千萬別開槍
- I'm taking a shot. - No! No. Don't do that.
沒事的
It's okay.
冷靜
Hey, calm down.
這裡是十六號  請求增援
This is 16! I need help!
蠢貨
Dumbass!
-鑰匙呢   -我不知道
- Where are the keys - I don't know.
他們只留下了車和無線電給我
They just left me here with just the car and the radio.
他媽的
Fuck!
-你確定嗎   -是的
- Are you sure - Yes.
你在撒謊嗎
Are you lying
喂  孩子  放鬆點  好嗎
Hey, hey, kid, just relax, all right
十六號  十六號  是你嗎
Sixteen Sixteen, is that you
我們現在派人過去
We're going to send someone.
太他媽的好了
Yes! Fuck yes!
好啦  走吧  趕緊離開這裡
Let's move. Let's get it outta here.
-拿上他的無線電   -明白
- Grab his radio. - Got it.
給你一點忠告
Here's a little advice
-遠離這些人   -快點  走啦
- Get away from these men.  - Let's move!
-回家  離開這裡   -快走啦  教皇
- Go home. Get out of here. - Vamos, Pope!
你剛才給那個該死的小孩錢
Did you give that fucking kid money
他看見我們的臉的時候  我們就應該立刻幹掉他
We should have killed that kid as soon as he saw our faces.
我們不能再殺人了
We are not killing any more people.
我現在就告訴你  如果我們到了海邊  班尼要是不在
I'll tell you right now, if we get to that beach and Ben isn't there,
我他媽的就要殺人了
I'm fucking killing people.
好的  他會在的  操
All right, he'll be there. Fuck!
媽的
Shit.
操
Fuck.
-快點   -可以走了嗎
- Come on!Come on! - Can we go
這是怎麼回事
What the hell is this
媽的
Shit!
他們撞到車了
They crashed into us!
聽好  小心點  他們朝海邊去了
Look out, be careful! They're heading to the beach.
他們剛剛過去
They just passed.
-所有人去棕櫚樹那邊   -他說什麼
- Everybody head towards the palm trees. - What did he say
-更多人來了   -那有兩輛車
- More are coming. - There's two vehicles!
好吧  我們應該馬上到海邊了
All right, it should open up onto the beach any minute.
教皇  開槍
Pope, shoot!
操
Fuck!
向司機開槍
Shoot the driver!
你有毛病嗎
What is wrong with you
-左邊   -離遠點  他們在開槍
- Left!  - They're firing! Give some room!
跟在後面
Stay behind!
他們跟著我們
They're right on us!
他們在哪裡
Where are they
左邊
Left! Left!
Left!
該死的
Goddamn!
到海灘了
All right, here's the beach.
他去哪裡了  你看見他了嗎
Where is he Do you see him
沒有  但是說好碰頭的海灣  離這裡還有一個半公里
No, but the cove where we're supposed to meet him's about a mile up this beach.
教皇  幹掉他們
Pope, kill them!
快幹掉他們
Just kill them!
他在那裡
There it is!
-我們要揮手讓他過來嗎   -沒錯
- Do I wave him in - Hell yeah!
去那邊
Go!
看來路到頭了
It looks like this is the end of the road.
看來是的
I see it.
我們穿過沙丘
We gotta cross over the dune!
穿過沙丘
Cross over the dune!
快走
Let's go!
快
Come on!
除去花銷和我們的服務費
Minus the expenses, and our administrative fee,
還剩下533萬4120美元
that leaves $5,334,120...
分五份
cut five ways.
也就是每份106萬6824美元
Which gives you five shares of $1,066,824.
我還需要你們每個人  在這第五份合約上面簽名
Oh, and I need all of your signatures on the fifth contract here.
它會把過世者的那一份  存進紅蒼蠅家庭基金
It'll deposit the deceased's share into the Redfly Family Trust.
給你
Here you are.
我想把我的那份也存進那個家庭基金
I'd like you to please include my share into the family trust.
我也是
Me, too.
謝謝
Thank you.
我會安排所有的財款放進家庭基金
So, I will schedule all the payments to the family trust.
當然
Of course.
謝謝  這是給你的
Thank you. That's for you.
謝謝  我們再聯繫
Thank you. I'll be in touch.
所以現在你們要做什麼
So, what are you guys gonna do now
我要回家
I gotta get home.
不能沒有這個
Not without these.
這個很有用
That'll help.
再見
See you.
多保重
Take care of yourself.
兄弟  再見
See you, buddy.
我愛你
Love you, man.
我也愛你
I love you, too.
-待會見  好嗎   -待會見
- I'll see you in a bit, all right - See you.
所以你接下來準備做什麼
So, what you gonna do now
我不知道
I don't know.
也許我會…
Maybe I'll, uh...
我會去澳大利亞找一個我認識的女孩
I'll go see this girl I know in Australia.
嗯  你應該去
Yeah, you should.
我聽說她最近弄了點錢
I hear she recently came into some money.
看樣子  她比我們所有人的結局
I guess she made out a whole hell of a lot better
都好得多
than any of us did.
似乎是這樣的
That seems about right.
等你看到茉莉和他女兒們…
When you see Molly and the girls...
告訴她們他是什麼樣的人
remind them who he was.
好  我會的
Yeah, I will.
多保重  好嗎
Take care of yourself, all right
你也是
You, too.
也許有一天我們可以用來做點好事
Maybe we can go do something good with it one day.